<resources>
    <string name="app_name">netcast</string>
    <string name="title_radio">NetCast</string>
    <string name="title_download">Download</string>
    <string name="title_podcast">Podcasts</string>
    <string name="title_favourites">Favourites</string>
    <string name="title_search">Search</string>
    <string name="radio_player">Net Cast Player</string>
    <string name="see_all">See All</string>
    <string name="hint_search">Search station,song,podcast</string>
    <string name="desccontent">imagesearch</string>
    <string name="title_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_welcome">Welcome To netcast \n Nice to have you here</string>
    <string name="title_activity_base">BaseActivity</string>
    <!-- Strings used for fragments for navigation -->
    <string name="first_fragment_label">First Fragment</string>
    <string name="second_fragment_label">Second Fragment</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>

    <string name="hello_first_fragment">Hello first fragment</string>
    <string name="hello_second_fragment">Hello second fragment. Arg: %1$s</string>
    <string name="all">See All</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="exo_download_notification_channel_name" />
    <string name="notification_Channel_Description">Netcast app notification manager</string>
    <string name="radio">Radio</string>
    <string name="ok">Ok</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="alarm_intent_action">from alarm</string>
    <string name="imprint">"Legal Disclosure Name and Physical Address of the Website Owner: Contact Information: Phone Number, Email and/or fax number. Registered office: Managing Director: Any registration and license numbers, including VAT  Court of Registration:  VAT-Number Sales Tax Identification Number: In accordance with Section 18 II of the German State Treaty on Broadcasting and Telemedia (MStV), we assume responsibility for the content of this website. Copyright Information Copyright All rights reserved. Online Dispute Resolution \"In accordance with Article 14(1) of the EU Regulation No 524/2013 on Online Dispute Resolution for consumers: The European Commission provides a platform for online dispute resolution, which you can find at https://webgate.ec.europa.eu/odr/. We do not participate in consumer arbitration board proceedings. This platform enables consumers to resolve disputes with online businesses in an efficient and impartial manner. "</string>
    <string name="faqs"><![CDATA["• Initial Steps<br/> • Account Related Queries<br/> • Apps and Devices<br/> • Technical Support<br/> • Contact Initial Steps 1.<br/> Is the app free to download and use? Yes, our app is available for free to download and use. However, some premium features may require a subscription or in-app purchase for access.<br/> 2. Is the Netcast app free? Absolutely! The Netcast app is free to download and use. As an advertising-funded service, we do not charge our users for listening to radio stations or podcasts on netcast.com. However, please keep in mind that you will need a stable internet connection to use netcast.com, and your service provider may charge you for data usage if you do not have an internet flat rate. To ensure the best user experience, we recommend using our app over Wi-Fi whenever possible, and pausing playback with the pause button when you are not actively using the app.<br/> 3. Can I stream live radio and podcasts on the app? Absolutely! Our app lets you tune in to live radio stations and podcasts from all over the world. You can explore and discover a wide variety of radio stations and podcasts, and enjoy them in realtime right from the app. 4. How can I search for radio stations or podcasts on the app? Searching for radio stations or podcasts on our app is easy. You can simply use the search bar or the search function to enter keywords, station/podcast names, or genres, and the app will provide you with relevant results that match your search criteria. 5. Can I create my own playlist of favorite radio stations or podcasts on the app? Yes, you can! Our app allows you to create a personalized playlist of your favorite radio stations or podcasts. You can add stations or podcasts to your playlist and organize them for convenient access and listening pleasure. 6. How can I share radio stations or podcasts with my friends using the app? Sharing radio stations or podcasts with your friends is easy with our app. You can utilize the builtin share feature within the app to send links or share on social media. Alternatively, you can simply copy the station or podcast URL and share it via other communication channels to share the content with your friends. 7. Does the app have an offline mode for listening to downloaded podcasts without an internet connection? Absolutely! Our app offers an offline mode that allows you to listen to downloaded podcasts without an internet connection. You can download your favorite podcasts for offline listening and enjoy them even when you are offline or in areas with limited internet connectivity.<br/> 8. Can I set a sleep timer on the app to automatically stop playback after a certain time? Yes, our app features a sleep timer that allows you to set a timer to automatically stop playback after a specified time. You can customize the sleep timer duration according to your preference, and the app will automatically pause or stop playback when the timer expires, making it convenient for bedtime listening or conserving battery life.<br/> 9. What is a podcast playlist? A podcast playlist is a curated collection of episodes from various podcast operators that revolve around a specific topic or theme. It allows you to listen to a series of episodes back-to-back, making it easy to discover and enjoy content on a particular subject. Tip: You also have the option to create your own personalized podcast playlist with your favorite episodes, giving you full control over your listening experience. Account 1. How do I manage my account and settings on the app, such as changing my password or email address? You can easily manage your account and settings within our app by accessing the account or settings section. From there, you can change your password, update your email address, and customize other settings to your preference. 2. Is my account information secure on the app? Yes, we take the security of your account information seriously. We utilize industry-standard security measures, including encryption and password hashing, to protect your account information. However, it's important to also use a strong and unique password for your account and keep your login credentials confidential to ensure maximum security. 3. Can I use the mobile app without creating an account? Yes, our mobile app allows you to listen to radio stations and podcasts without creating an account. Simply download the app from the app store, install it on your Android device, and start browsing and streaming radio stations and podcasts without needing to create an account. However, creating an account may provide additional features and benefits, such as the ability to save your favorite stations, create playlists, and customize your listening experience. It's optional and up to you whether you want to create an account or use the app as a guest user.<br/> 4. Where can I find my favorite stations on the app? Your favorite stations can be easily accessed under the Favorites tab, specifically under YOUR STATIONS -> Your favorites. This view provides a summary of your radio activity, showcasing your favorite stations as well as the stations you have recently listened to.<br/> 5. How can I add or delete favorite stations/podcasts? To add a station or podcast as a favorite or remove it, simply go to the detailed view of the station or podcast on the app and tap the heart icon located at the top right corner. Tapping the heart icon will save the station or podcast as a favorite, and tapping it again will remove it from your favorites. This feature allows you to easily manage and organize your favorite stations and podcasts for quick access and listening. Apps & Devices 1. Is there an option for an ad-free version of the app? Yes, we provide an alternative version called Netcast Premium that has fewer ads compared to the free version. With Netcast Premium, you won't see any ads from our side, including videos or banners. However, it's important to note that some radio stations may still broadcast their own audio ads before the start of, and during, their programs. These are known as pre-stream or in-stream advertisements, and unfortunately, we are unable to prevent these ads from being played by the stations themselves. We appreciate your understanding in this regard. 2. What type of content is available for offline streaming? Downloaded Podcast episodes are available for offline streaming. 3. What is Offline Listening? Offline listening allows you to download entire podcast episodes, making them available for playback without an internet connection, whenever you want. 4. How can I remove a recent station from my Home screen? On your Home screen, you'll find a list of recently played audio. To remove a station or podcast from the list, simply tap and hold the content's name or logo, and then select the \"Remove\" option. 5. How do I delete a downloaded podcast episode? To delete a downloaded podcast episode, first go to your Library and tap on Downloads. Then, tap the \"edit\" icon in the upper right corner and select the episode(s) you want to delete. Finally, tap the small trash icon in the upper right corner to remove the episode(s) from your device.<br/> 6. How can I find something to listen to? There are several ways to discover content to listen to: If you have specific stations or podcasts in mind, you can tap the \"Search\" icon at the top of the app. The Home section lets you browse through content you've recently played, as well as a live feed of new episodes from podcasts you like, and personalized recommendations based on your listening habits. You can also swipe through audio categories like Local Radio, Sports, News & Talk, Music, and more at the top of the Home screen.<br/> 7. How do I download the Netcast app? To download the Netcast app on your Android device, simply go to your carrier's app store (such as Google Play Store or Amazon App Store) and search for \"Netcast.\" Once the app is installed, you can start listening to Netcast's selection of radio, music, news, sports, and more. Creating a Netcast account will also enable better recommendations and allow you to access your listening history across all your devices. Technical Support 1. I would like to configure a sleep timer. There are three methods to set the sleep timer: If you have selected a station from the list and the detailed view opens, you will see a circle with three dots located to the right of the play-pause symbol. Within this circle, you can access the sleep timer function, among other options. Another way to set the sleep timer is through the app settings, which can be accessed by clicking on the user icon at the top left corner of each main screen. In the app settings, you will find the alarm clock and sleep timer options at the top, just below the welcome message. You can also open the player in full-screen view by tapping on the player at the bottom of the screen. Within the full-screen view, you will find the circle with three dots to the right of the playpause button, which you can use to set the sleep timer. 2. How to close the app completely? There are two common methods to completely quit the app on Android: Open the multi-app view and swipe away the app. Use the Android task manager to close the app. 3. I would like to configure an alarm. There are two methods to set an alarm: After selecting the desired station and opening the detailed view, click on the alarm icon located to the right of the play button. Alternatively, you can access the alarm clock through the side menu by clicking on the menu icon located at the top left corner, or by swiping from the left side of the screen towards the middle. 4. Unable to find the station If you have been unable to find a station using the search function located at the top right side of the page, even after trying different spellings, please contact us via the support button, which can be found to the right or beneath the FAQs. Please provide us with the exact name of the station, the city where the station is based, and ideally the station's website. We will make every effort to make the station available as soon as possible. Contact & Feedback 1. I wish to promote my music or event Netcast.com is not a radio station and we are unable to forward messages to stations or influence broadcast content. Kindly reach out to the relevant station directly for any promotional inquiries or requests. 2. How I can contact a particular radio station? Netcast.com does not function as a radio station. We do not have the ability to forward messages to stations or influence broadcast content. For any inquiries or requests, kindly contact the relevant station directly. 3. Can I report bugs or issues with the app? Yes, you can usually report bugs or issues with the app using the \"Feedback\" or \"Contact Us\" option in the app's settings or menu. Be sure to provide detailed information about the issue, including steps to reproduce it and any error messages you encountered. 4. Can I suggest new features or improvements for the app? Yes, many app developers welcome suggestions for new features or improvements. You can provide your suggestions using the \"Feedback\" or \"Contact Us\" option in the app's settings or menu. Be specific and explain how the new feature or improvement would benefit the app and its users. 5. What should I do if I encounter a technical issue with the app? If you encounter a technical issue with the app, you can report it using the \"Feedback\" or \"Contact Us\" option in the app's settings or menu. Provide as much information as possible about the issue, including the device and operating system you're using, the app version, and any error messages or screenshots. "]]></string>

</resources>